Guide to the Dorothy Allison Papers, 1965-2010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Subject Files Series, 1974-1998 and undated, (31 boxes)
  - Pornography Subseries
    - Elshtain, Jean Bethke. The Victim Syndrome. (Box 16)
    - Buckley, Christopher (Box 16)
    - Webster, Paula. Pornography and Pleasure. (Box 16)
    - Feminists Against Pornography: D.C. (Box 16)
    - Porn Violence Linked to Aggression (Box 16)
    - Filthy Lucre: Henry Schipper, Sex Porn and Male Rage, 1980. (Box 16)
    - Soft Porn in Soft Covers, 1983. (Box 16)
    - Irene Diamond: Pornography and Repression: A Reconsideration. (Box 16)
    - Women in Print List, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Women in S& M, Character sketches (Box 16)
    - Lesbian Sex Mafia (5 folders) (Box 16)
    - S/M party at D's (Box 16)
    - Derricotte, Toi (Box 16)
    - Pornography Law (Box 16)
    - S/M The Last Closet (Box 16)
    - Lenzer, Jeanne. Sex, Sexism or Pornography Independent, Durham, NC. (Box 16)
    - Dworkin/Stoltenberg.Joining hands in the fight against pornography. (Box 16)
    - Lesbian S/M (Box 16)
    - Hellfire Club (Box 16)
    - The Asstrick (Box 16)
    - Wynter, Sarah. Whisper. (Box 16)
    - Looking and Not Looking: Porn and Erotic Photography. (Box 16)
    - Goldman, Daniel. New York Psychiatric Syndromes Spur Protest, 1985. (Box 16)
    - The Girls of Rock and Roll, Playboy. (Box 16)
    - S/M and the Myth of Mutual Consent (Box 16)
    - Firing Line transcript: William Buckley, Andrea Dworkin and Harriet Pilpel (Box 16)
    - America Booksellers v. William Hudnut, Mayor of the City of Indianapolis, IN (Box 16)
    - Women Against Censorship Review (Box 16)
    - Decrow, Karen. Strange Bedfellows. (Box 16)
    - F.A.C.T. slideshow (Box 16)
    - Conditions Review (Box 16)
    - Towards a View of Sex Prejudice (Box 16)
    - Power and Trust Women's S/M in Amsterdam (Box 16)
    - Is One Woman's Sexuality Another Woman's Pornography? Ms. Magazine. (Box 16)
    - Their Cheap Thrills Are Killing Us (Box 16)
    - Self and Self Image, Gay Left. (Box 16)
    - Gregory Battcock: A Queer Death (Box 16)
    - Torture (News: females shave secretary of Playboy) (Box 16)
    - S/M Letters, Information sheet (Box 16)
    - Burstyn, Varda. Porn Again, Fuse Magazine. (Box 16)
    - Wildcats: Women Bikers (Box 16)
    - Leather Lifestyle Conference (Box 17)
    - MacKinnon, Catharine. Not a Moral Issue. (Box 17)
    - French, Marilyn on Andrea Dworkin, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Hunt, Margaret. Feminism, Sex and Power, 1987. (Box 17)
    - Rose, Toni with Howard Smith. Dialogue with a Dominatrix, 1979. (Box 17)
    - Levine, Art, and Kathleen Curie. Whip Me, Beat Me, Cancel My NOW Membership, 1987. (Box 17)
    - S/M London (Box 17)
    - Coverage of Meese Commission (Box 17)
    - Pornomaniac Moral Majority, 1986 (Box 17)
    - The Meese Commission on the Road, 1986. (Box 17)
    - Critical Reviews of Andrea Dworkin (Box 17)
    - S/M Survey (Box 17)
    - Pornography Bibliography (Box 17)
    - Stern, Leslie. The Body as Evidence, 1983. (Box 17)
    - The Spinster and Her Enemies (Box 17)
    - Feminist Anti-Censorship Task Force: F.A.C.T. (Box 17)
    - Raab, Lawrence (Box 17)
    - Sex Conference at Barnard, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Barry, Kathleen. Sadomasochism: The New Backlash to Feminism. (Box 17)
    - Carpenter, Tessa. Women and Erotica, 1983. (Box 17)
    - Gordone, Charles (Box 17)
    - WAP vs. Willis Letters (Box 17)
    - Women Against Pornography NYC (Box 17)
    - Porn and Female Self Image: Speak Out (Box 17)
    - Brownmiller, Jong and Goldstein on pornography, 1984 (Box 17)
    - W.A.P. Parody: Unconscionable X-Women (Box 17)
    - Co-opting Women (Box 17)
  - Paglia, Camille (Box 18)
  - Parker, Pat (Box 18)
  - Pally, Marcia. The Fireworks at the Sexuality Conference, 1982. (Box 18)
  - Parton, Dolly (Box 18)
  - Pies, Stacy, writings (Box 18)
  - Cindy Patton on the role of the gay press in AIDS, 1988 (Box 18)
  - PEN Magazine (Box 18)
  - Women Pedophiles? (Box 18)
  - Penelope, Julia (Box 18)
  - Peterson, James R. Why the Movies Don't Work for Me. (Box 18)
  - Piehard, Georges. Drie Ondeugende Dochters. (Box 18)
  - Piercy, Marge. Particolored Blocks for a Quilt. (Box 18)
  - Pizarnik, Alejandra. The Bloody Countess. (Box 18)
  - Post Office Entrapment and Censorship, Playboy. (Box 18)
  - Powers of Desire (Box 18)
  - Pratt, Minnie Bruce, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Press Gang Publishers (Box 18)
  - Preston, John (Box 18)
  - Price, Reynolds (Box 18)
  - Primitive Social Organization (Box 18)
  - Prostitution (Box 18)
  - Pearl, Julie. Costs of Prosecuting Prostitutes. (Box 18)
  - Gay and Lesbian Publishing Triangle (Box 18)
  - Publisher's Weekly Review (Box 18)
  - Queer Nation (Box 18)
  - I hate Straights Queer Nation (Box 18)
  - QSM (Box 18)
  - Queer Theory, Santa Cruz, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Radical Faeries (Box 18)
  - Podlosky, Robin, Los Angeles (Box 18)
  - Rapp, Rayna, and Ellen Ross. Compulsory Heterosexuality. (Box 18)
  - S/M Book from Rayna (Box 18)
  - New Stories from the South, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Rechy, John. The Ghettoization of Gay Art. (Box 18)
  - Dorothy's Red Velvet Cake (Box 18)
  - Reisman, Judith, Playboy (Box 18)
  - Rheims, Bettina, photographer of women (Box 18)
  - Anne Rice: American Fantasy Interview (Box 18)
  - Rich, Adrienne. When We Dead Awaken. (Box 18)
  - Rich, B. Ruby. Anti-Porn: Soft issue, hard world. (Box 18)
  - Riggs, Marlon (Box 18)
  - Riley, Barbara and Dorothy Child (Box 19)
  - Rise, Darrell Yates on AIDS (Box 19)
  - Rubson, Ruthann (Box 19)
  - Romo-Carmona, Mariana (Box 19)
  - Rosenfeld, Dana (Box 19)
  - Roy, Camille. Lesbian Sex in the 80s, 1988. (Box 19)
  - Rubin, Gayle. Misguided, Dangerous and Wrong ... porn, NOW Testimony (Box 19)
  - Rushin, Kate (Box 19)
  - Russ, Joanna.Porn by Women for Women with Love. (Box 19)
  - Russo, Vito (Box 19)
  - Ruth, Barbara (Box 19)
  - Sadomasochism Subseries
    This suberies contains Allison's research files on sadomasochism (S/M).
    - International Ms. Leather (IMSL), 1989 (Box 19)
    - Board Bios, IMSL (Box 19)
    - Lesbian Sex Mafia (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Club Domentia - Whitefeather (Box 19)
    - Women's S/M groups (Box 19)
    - The Leather Institute, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Did you See? GMSMA (Box 19)
    - Reeves, Tom. Loving Boys. (Box 19)
    - Tsang, Dan. Men and Boys: The Boston Conference. (Box 19)
    - The Vault, NYC, formerly Hellfire (Box 19)
    - Cellblock 28 28, 9th Ave., NYC (Box 19)
    - Everett, Karen. Trading Secrets. (Box 19)
    - Lesbian and Gay Community Center, NYC (Box 19)
    - Leather and Blues Motorcycle Club (Box 19)
    - The Outcasts (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Women's Press, Toronto, Canada (Box 19)
    - NLA May Day, Seattle, 1988 (Box 20)
    - Marks, David Samuel (Box 20)
    - National March on Washington request for proposals (Box 20)
    - Journal of Sexual Liberty (Box 20)
    - Nozzle Talk (Box 20)
    - Lesbian Sex Mafia Bylaws (Box 20)
    - S/M Women's Support Groups, Briar Rose handout (Box 20)
    - Eulenspiegel (Box 20)
    - Gay and Lesbian erotic videos (Advocate handout) (Box 20)
    - Sub Mittance--Terry Yeary, Atlanta, GA (Box 20)
    - GMSMA Expulsion (Box 20)
    - Outcasts Letter to GMSMA (Box 20)
    - Bisexual News, Views and Networking, Long Beach, CA (Box 20)
    - National Leather Association (Box 20)
    - GMSMA (Gay Male S/M Activists) (Box 20)
    - Sandmutopia Guardian (Box 20)
    - Interview with a masochist, Christopher Street, 1980 (Box 20)
    - Pally, Marcia. Women in Porn, 1987. (Box 20)
    - Japanese Cross Dressing (Box 20)
    - TIN S/M Newsletter, SF, CA (Box 20)
    - The 15, Torture Times (Box 20)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF) Privacy Project Fact Sheet (Box 20)
    - Congdon, Kirby (Box 20)
    - Rage, Christopher (Box 20)
    - Nisson, Master George II, Dungeon Design and Custom Adult Toys (Box 20)
    - Women Organized Against Pornography and Prostitution (Box 20)
    - Roy, Camille. Feminism and the Politics of Sex, 1987. (Box 20)
    - Hirschfeld, Magnus (Box 20)
    - Huddleston, Marion (Box 20)
    - The Leather Faerie Directory (Box 20)
    - PEP: People Exchanging Power, Silver Spring, MD (Box 20)
    - DADS: Denver Area Dominants and Submissives (Box 20)
    - Dennon, Stacy (Box 20)
    - S/M Mailing List, Dallas (Box 20)
    - National Leather Association: Seattle (Box 20)
    - S/M Rough Sex, Mademoiselle, 1987. (Box 20)
    - Stein, David. New York Native on Dallas, 1988. (Box 20)
    - Sexuality and Stigmatized Sex Bibliography and Workshop Questions (Box 20)
    - The Porno Plague, 1976. (Box 20)
    - S/M: Shall I Compare Thee to a Battered Wife? 1980. (Box 20)
    - Diski, Jenny. S/M: Nothing Natural. (Box 20)
    - Schrim, Janet. S/M: Is it Oppression? (Box 20)
    - S/M Womanews Letters (Box 20)
    - Giangregorio, Michael. I love S/M, 1981. (Box 20)
    - S/M Clubs, NYC Forum (Box 20)
    - Sexpo 1982 (Box 20)
    - REX, S/M Faggot Artist (Box 20)
    - Mistress, Wildfire Club Periodical (Box 20)
    - Popert, Ken. Cruising and Crisis Management, 1980. (Box 20)
    - Samois. Plexus, 1980. (Box 20)
    - McCormack, Thelma. Censorship, Access, and the Politics of Porn, 1983. (Box 20)
    - Not a Love Story and the Anti-Porn Crusade (Box 20)
    - The BMR Collective (Box 21)
    - S/M Atlanta Group Meetings (Box 21)
    - S/M Mariana Valverde. Body Politic, 1980. (Box 21)
    - GMSMA: Gay Men's S/M Alliance, NYC (Box 21)
    - On Our Backs (Box 21)
    - The Scholar and the Feminist IX: Towards a Politics of Sexuality, 1982. (Box 21)
    - Semiotext (Box 21)
    - Urania Interview (Box 21)
    - So What Do You Want to Talk About Anyway? (Box 21)
    - Coming to Power (Box 21)
    - Caplan, Paula J. The Myth of Women's Masochism. (Box 21)
    - Cathexis (Box 21)
    - Against Sadomasochism (Box 21)
    - S/M Sex in the Open Chateau 19 (Box 21)
    - Andrea Dworkin. The Prophet of Perversion, 1980. (Box 21)
    - All Tied Up: Heterosexual S/M (Box 21)
    - Masochist jokes (Box 21)
    - Serena, female dominant (Box 21)
    - The Rigid Bondage Roster (Box 21)
    - Glanzberg, F.G. Lesbian Sadomasochists: Rattling the skeletons. (Box 21)
    - Off our Backs: LSM notice (Box 21)
    - Kat Match S/M (Box 21)
    - The sex life of the foot and shoe bibliography (Box 21)
    - Plexus S/M articles and letters (Box 21)
    - Benjamin, Jessica. Rational Violence and Erotic Domination. (Box 21)
    - Libra, R.J. SM: One Woman peers through the prism. (Box 21)
    - Verdenignig Studiegroep Sado-Masochism (V.S.S.M) Amsterdam S/M group (Box 21)
    - Witomski, T.R. S/M Nation, 1984. (Box 21)
    - Gay male S/M activists (Box 21)
    - Schrim, J.A. SM and Feminism. (Box 21)
    - Drummer clubs/bars (gay men's SM) (Box 21)
    - Cathexis (Box 21)
    - Gay Male S/M (Box 21)
    - Frankel, Linda. The Children's Hour. (Box 21)
    - Cottingham, Laura. If God is a Woman then Andrea Dworkin is her Wrath. (Box 21)
    - If I ask you to tie me up, will you still love me? (Box 21)
    - Prometheus - Pat Bond (Box 21)
    - Dungeon Master (Box 21)
    - Townsend, Larry (Box 22)
    - Miesen, Donald. A View of the Sadomasochism, the adult sex game. (Box 22)
    - The Society of Janus (SF) (Box 22)
    - Review of Coming to Power (Box 22)
    - Dominatrix of Doom: Plasmatics, 1981. (Box 22)
    - S& M Rock (Box 22)
    - Censorship (Box 22)
    - Sex, Porn and Male Rage, 1980. (Box 22)
    - Women Who Resist: Santa Cruz women against rape (Box 22)
    - Sheiner, C.J. (Box 22)
    - Novak, Nancy. Wrestling Dominant. (Box 22)
    - WHIPS: Women's Music Festival S/M Group (Box 22)
    - Hollibaugh, Amber - Sex Work (Box 22)
    - Jeffreys, Sheila. The Sexuality Debate, review by Mariana Valverde (Box 22)
    - Folsom Street Fair, South of Market (Box 22)
    - Avatar (Box 22)
    - Goldstein, Richard ... Sex (Box 22)
    - International Ms. Leather (Box 22)
    - Slater, Cynthia. Sensual Magic. (Box 22)
    - Powell, Mason. Bound for Glory. (Box 22)
    - Wiomski, T.R. (Box 22)
    - Rubin, Gayle (Box 22)
    - S/M Letters (Box 22)
    - Davis, Murray. Smut, Part One (Box 22)
    - Barker, Edna. Confessions of a Skirt Chaser. (Box 22)
    - Sexual Fantasies: What are Their Hidden Meanings? 1984. (Box 22)
    - Carnival Knowledge (Box 22)
    - Heresy, Witchcraft and Sexuality (Box 22)
    - Powers of Desire Pro-sex reviews (Box 22)
    - The other AIDS story: Quarantine! (Box 22)
    - Autoerotic strangulation deaths, 1984 (Box 22)
    - Vance, Carol. Sexuality Bibliographies. (Box 22)
    - Vibrators (Box 22)
    - Catholic Church: No Sex, No Wedding, 1982. (Box 22)
    - Village Voice sex ads (Box 22)
    - DeCecco, John P. Pleasure and Queers, 1981. (Box 22)
    - Durden-Smith, Jo and Diane De Simone. The Sex Life of the Brain. (Box 22)
    - Golding. A Few Thoughts about Lesbian Sex, Politics and Community Standards. (Box 22)
    - Freedom, Sex, and Power: Interviews with Charlotte Bunch, George Smith, Chris Bearchell, Gary Kinsman, Susan Colek, and Varda Burstyn. Fuse (Box 22)
    - Lesbian Erotic Questionnaire - Sapphic Touch (Box 22)
    - M.M. Malafesta. In Search of the Cosmic Orgasm, 1981. (Box 22)
    - Sexuality, Gender and Consumer Culture: NY Institute for the Humanities (Box 22)
    - Nestle, Joan: Sexuality, S/M, Pornography Bibliography (Box 22)
    - Women against porn script for slideshow (Box 22)
    - Gross, Michael. Sex Sells, 1985. (Box 23)
    - Bearchell, Chris. Strippers: No Apologies. (Box 23)
    - Lesbian Sex on Video, 1986. (Box 23)
    - Tye originally Fantasy: She Might (Box 23)
    - S/M is ... (Box 23)
    - S/M Bibliography (Box 23)
    - Heaney, Seamus. Punishment. (Box 23)
    - Baldwin, Guy and Race (Richard) Bannon - Survey of S/M practices (Box 23)
    - Paris S/M Community, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Descending adults NY S/M (Box 23)
    - Golstein, Al, S/M (Box 23)
  - Sagaris (Box 23)
  - Samois (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - San Francisco Art Institute (Box 23)
  - Santa Cruz (Box 23)
  - The Pillory and The Closet (Box 23)
  - Joy Schulenberg's novel (Box 23)
  - Schulman, Sarah (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Seal Press (Box 23)
  - The Scholar and The Feminist, 1982 (Box 23)
  - See, Carolyn (Box 23)
  - Segrest, Mab (Box 23)
  - Sears, Vicki (Box 23)
  - Serial Killers (Box 23)
  - Private Sex Clubs, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Sex and evolution sociobiology (Box 23)
  - Sex and social repression conference 1988 (Box 23)
  - Shakur, Assata (Box 23)
  - Sheen, Barbara (Box 23)
  - Shelix (Box 23)
  - Shilts, Randy (Box 23)
  - Shively, Charlie. Fag Rag History. (Box 23)
  - Sino, Ana Maria (Box 23)
  - Simpson, Mona (Box 23)
  - Simpson, Mona. Lawns. (Box 24)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis. The Impresario, 1986. (Box 24)
  - Sky Renfro and Leather (Box 24)
  - Slater, Cynthia (Box 24)
  - Smith, Barbara (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Smith, Charlie (Box 24)
  - Smith, Lee (Box 24)
  - Snitow, Ann on Doris Lessing, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Sontag, Susan. The Third World of Women. (Box 24)
  - Counts, Sora (Box 24)
  - South, Cris (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Edgefield County, South Carolina (Box 24)
  - Modern Southern Writers, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Stamps, Wickie (Box 24)
  - Stained glass (Box 24)
  - Stanford Writing Program (Box 24)
  - Stanley, Julia. Uninhabited Angels. (Box 24)
  - Female Star Trek Fans (Box 24)
  - Steele, Shirley. Ruby, You're Like a Dream. (Box 24)
  - Stein, Arlene, on Style Wars (Box 24)
  - Stein, David. My Weekend in Hell. (Box 24)
  - Steiner, George. A Season in Hell. (Box 24)
  - Stein, Gertrude. The Mother of Us All. (Box 24)
  - Stengel, Richard. Talking about my GeneratioN, 1987. (Box 24)
  - Stewart, Sam, on Valentino (Box 24)
  - Stoltenberg, John. Good Sex and Gay Male Porn, 1983. (Box 24)
  - Stone, Robert. The Reason for Stories, 1988. (Box 24)
  - Stonewall Anniversary (Box 24)
  - Stretching exercises (Box 24)
  - Sweet Gwendolyn and the Countess: soft porn drawing and story (Box 24)
  - Syllabuses (Box 24)
  - Tattoo archives, Berkeley, CA (Box 24)
  - Tax traps for homesellers (Box 24)
  - Thelma and Louise (Box 24)
  - Thompson, Sharon, fiction, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Tipton, Billy (Box 24)
  - Trebay, Guy (Box 24)
  - Person, Ethel S. Love Triangles, 1988. (Box 24)
  - Trivia (Box 24)
  - Trujillo, Carla, Chicana Lesbian Ph.D. (Box 24)
  - Tsui, Kitty (Box 24)
  - Tucker, Scott (Box 24)
  - Underground parties - LA (Box 25)
  - Vacations (Box 25)
  - Valverde, Mariana. The True Joy of Sex. (Box 25)
  - Fiction Vampires (Box 25)
  - Van de Vere, Judy (Box 25)
  - Vance, Carol. Wages for Fellatio. (Box 25)
  - Van Sant, Gus (Box 25)
  - Village Voice Writers/Union members (Box 25)
  - Villanueva, Chea. Girlfriends and Chinagirls (Box 25)
  - Voice Literary Supplement, 1986-1989 (Box 25)
  - Oppenheim, Irene.On Waitressing, 1986. (Box 25)
  - Alice Walker National Book Award Speech, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Walters, Anna Mae. The Sun is not Merciful. (Box 25)
  - Warhol, Andy (Box 25)
  - Warland, Betsy, lesbian writers (Box 25)
  - WAP News Report (Box 25)
  - Wavpam forum on S/M San Francisco Samois Flier Protesting (Box 25)
  - Webster, Paula. Going All the Way to Pleasure. (Box 25)
  - Weeks, Jeffrey. British Gay Left and Organizing. (Box 25)
  - Women of Value, Men of Renown (Box 25)
  - Weinstein, Jeff. What porn did. (Box 25)
  - Weldon, Fay (Box 25)
  - Wells, Jess (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Wesleyan University (Box 25)
  - White, Edmund (Box 25)
  - White, James (Box 25)
  - WHIPS at Michigan, 1988 (Box 25)
  - White Working Class Sojourner Issue, November, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Wilde, Dolly/Joan Schenkar (Box 25)
  - Williams, Tennessee. Desire and the black master. (Box 25)
  - Willis, Danielle (Box 25)
  - Willis, Ellen (Box 25)
  - Wilson, William (Box 25)
  - Winterson, Jeanette (Box 25)
  - Wolff, Tobias (Box 25)
  - Wolfe, Tom (Box 25)
  - Wolverton, Terry (Box 25)
  - Women's Art, 1987 (Box 26)
  - French, Marilyn on Marilyn Hacker - The Nation of Women (Box 26)
  - Michelson, Peter. Women and pornorotica, 1986. (Box 26)
  - Women in Print (Box 26)
  - Women Organized to Make Abuse Nonexistent, Inc. (W.o.m.a.n.), SF (Box 26)
  - Women against Sex (Box 26)
  - Wojnarwicz, David W. (Box 26)
  - Words Project for AIDS (Box 26)
  - Working Class Women's Caucus UFF (Box 26)
  - Writer's rejection letters (Box 26)
  - First Novels (Box 26)
  - Goodbye minimalists, hello tellers of tall tales, 1989. (Box 26)
  - Yoakam, Dwight (Box 26)
  - Youngblood, Shay (Box 26)
  - Youngdahl, Karie. The cutting line (Box 26)
  - Yellow Silk fiction/poetry (Box 26)
  - Zimmerman, Bonnie (Box 26)
  - Zschokke, Magdalene (Box 26)
  - Subject Files Subseries, Non-alphabetical
    These boxes contain Allison's subject files that were received in non-alphabetical order.
    - Murphy, Melissa (Box 27)
    - D'Erasmo, Stacey (Box 27)
    - Impact - lesbian writers (Box 27)
    - Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies - CLAGS (Box 27)
    - Writer's Union (Box 27)
    - Diva (Box 27)
    - Subscriptions (Box 27)
    - Thomas, Trish (Box 27)
    - Weathers, Annette (Box 27)
    - Logan, Becket (Box 27)
    - Seajay, Carol, writing class (Box 27)
    - Lesbian S/M Safety Manual (Box 27)
    - Nazi History Philipp Jenniger resigns after speech (Box 27)
    - Working class writing - Spring at the lab (Box 27)
    - Kenan, Randall (Box 27)
    - Margeaux/The Lab (Box 27)
    - Lesbian writer (Box 27)
    - Corporal punishment, 1987 (Box 27)
    - Lesbian erotica review, 1987 (Box 27)
    - Tucker, Scott (Box 27)
    - Workshop/panel request for Outrite, 1990 (Box 27)
    - Poetry clippings from Outweek (Box 27)
    - Survey of writers: what do I do when I write? (Box 27)
    - Kafka, Franz. Josephine the Singer. (Box 27)
    - O'Brien, Tim. Sweetheart of Song Tra Bong. (Box 27)
    - Performance art (Box 27)
    - Tompkins, Jane (Box 28)
    - Women in literature (Box 28)
    - The Daydream of Bloody Seriousness, 1982. (Box 28)
    - Sex and violence, death and sensuality (Box 28)
    - A Rock in the Middle of the Ocean, Advocate. (Box 28)
    - Maunter Project: lesbians with cancer (Box 28)
    - Paulson, Kevin (Box 28)
    - Ringelheim, Joan, women and the Holocaust (Box 28)
    - Resume (Box 28)
    - On our backs contract (Box 28)
    - Women Who Hate Me contract (Box 28)
    - Lace Publications (Box 28)
    - Alyson Press (Box 28)
    - Escoffier, Jeff, literary agent (Box 28)
    - Submitted for consideration (Box 28)
    - Maryse Conde Conference (Box 28)
    - Bastard out of Carolina reviews (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Seabrook, John. The AIDS Philosopher, 1990. (Box 28)
    - International Ms. Leather, Drummer (Box 28)
    - Radical Voices syllabus (Box 28)
    - The battle over quality (Box 28)
    - Thompson, Mark. Leatherfolk. (Box 28)
    - Lawrence of Arabia and S/M Advocate, 1989. (Box 28)
    - Barthelme, Donald (Box 28)
    - Who are the outcasts? history handout (Box 28)
    - Feminist political theory at George Washington University (Box 28)
    - The Women Who Hate Me (Box 28)
    - Flesh and fantasy workshop (Box 28)
    - NEA grant application (Box 28)
    - Oberland, Wendy, camerawork (Box 28)
    - Women studies, UC Berkeley, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Sex with Dorothy Allison IAHU Wesleyan College (Box 28)
    - Voice Literary Supplement, Oct. 1986 (Box 28)
    - Society for the Scientific Study of Sex (SSSS) (Box 29)
    - Strega, Linda and Bev Jo. S/M is Sadism and Masochism is Heterosexism (Box 29)
    - Hentoff, Nat. The First State to Abolish Obscenity, 1987. (Box 29)
    - American Booksellers Association vs. Indianapolis (Box 29)
    - Skin draft (Box 29)
    - Trash cover (Box 29)
    - The pornographic imperative (Box 29)
    - Astrea - lesbian writer's fund (Box 29)
    - Paulson, Kevin (Box 29)
    - Nashville (Box 29)
    - Gartwell, Nanette. Feminist Ethics. (Box 29)
    - Carruthers, Lisa. Ex-Isle. (Box 29)
    - My most unforgettable character ... (Box 29)
    - Outwrite, 1989-1991 (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Personal revelation (Box 29)
    - Women and the Law (Box 29)
    - Working Class, Lesbian, Femme: Three Strikes You're Out (Box 29)
    - Events ... organizations (Box 29)
    - Heavy pain and blood sports (Box 30)
    - Cheap thrills Forum essay (Box 30)
    - How to Date a Dildo (Box 30)
    - Allison, Dorothy. The Deviation Doctor. (Box 30)
    - What She Did With Her Hands, 1988 (Box 30)
    - Gibson, Mattie Lee (Box 30)
    - A Lesbian Review of Trash (Box 30)
    - The Female Dominant S/M Community (Box 30)
    - The Power of Names (Box 30)
    - Cultural Survival and Cultural Work (Box 30)
    - Feminist theory course with Charlotte Bunch, George Washington University, 1976 (Box 30)
    - On Key Symbols (Box 30)
    - Smith, Jamez L. poems (Box 30)
    - Wolochow, Dara. Behind our Backs. (Box 30)
    - Deviant sexuality (Box 30)
    - Houston, Angelica (Box 31)
    - Bastard Out of Carolina Showtime (Box 31)
    - Hoffman, Gary (Box 31)
    - 1st Day of School, Ladies' Home Journal. (Box 31)
    - Mother Child Bond, Out Magazine. (Box 31)
    - Lee, Andrea. The Emperor of Dreams, 1997. (Box 31)
    - Curve, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Mayer, Peter - Overlook (Box 31)
    - Bastard Nation (Box 31)
    - C-TAN - Circlet (Box 31)
    - Garber, Eric (Box 31)
    - Aury, Dominique. Story of O. (Box 31)
    - Califia, Pat. Radical Sex. (Box 31)
    - Anders, Allison (Box 31)
    - Thomas, Trish (Box 31)
    - Willis, Connie (Box 31)
    - Gwenwald, Morgan (Box 31)
    - Sarris, Greg (Box 31)
    - Jetter, Alexis (Box 31)
    - Kincaid, Jamaica (Box 31)
    - Kirn, Walter. Mouth to Mouth. (Box 31)
    - Sinclair, Molly (Box 31)
    - Willalon, Joel Antonia (Box 31)
    - Erotic content in women's art (Box 31)
    - Women writing sex workshop (Box 31)
    - Writing workshop flier master (Box 31)
    - No! (Box 31)
    - Sankey, Gretchen - artist (Box 31)
    - Williams, Tennessee and Maria St. Just (Box 31)